<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Continuously updated on Kambri's Blog</title><link>https://kambri.top/en/categories/%E6%8C%81%E7%BB%AD%E6%9B%B4%E6%96%B0/</link><description>Recent content in Continuously updated on Kambri's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Kaige ZHENG</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kambri.top/en/categories/%E6%8C%81%E7%BB%AD%E6%9B%B4%E6%96%B0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello World!</title><link>https://kambri.top/en/p/welcome/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kambri.top/en/p/welcome/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://kambri.top/p/welcome/img/cover.jpg" alt="Featured image of post Hello World!" /&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⚠️ Please note that the content here was translated by a large language model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id="welcome"&gt;Welcome——
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Welcome to my life &amp;amp; tech blog! A solitary life also needs to maintain a sense of outward expression. I wanted to satisfy some &amp;ldquo;desire to share&amp;rdquo; in a place not constrained by content and form, so I established this site at the end of 2024 and have been exploring and improving it since. Initially, I quickly built a blog using Hugo and the Stack theme template, writing some life records and tech shares. Later, I realized that most of my tech shares were not efficient (neither spreading some novel thoughts nor fully serving as a knowledge repository for me). At the beginning of 2026, I rebuilt the blog based on the &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/CaiJimmy/hugo-theme-stack/releases/tag/v3.33.0" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;v3.33.0&lt;/a&gt; branch of Stack and made some modifications with my limited front-end skills according to my ideas. This time, I plan to focus on life archiving (such as recording travel experiences, sharing annual summaries, etc.) and occasionally write some reflections on research. Due to limited energy, I may not write or update very frequently, and of course, the text and form will be more casual. Additionally, I have set up a &lt;a class="link" href="https://gallery.kambri.top/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;personal photo album&lt;/a&gt;, hoping to archive some meaningful photos, temporarily named &lt;strong&gt;Cached Memory&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Probably not many people will see this blog; I will only share it within a certain range of friends, though it also supports Bing and Google searches. So, the main purpose of writing the blog is to record life and entertain myself. Anyway, no matter how you accessed here, I feel honored. &lt;strong&gt;Your arrival is also part of the reason I created this blog.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="some-tips"&gt;Some Tips
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you want to check out other blogs, please click &lt;a class="link" href="https://kambri.top/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;; if you want to know more about me and this site, please click &lt;a class="link" href="https://kambri.top/about/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;; if you want to categorize blog posts by tags, please click &lt;a class="link" href="https://kambri.top/archives/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;; if you want to search for interesting content by title or keyword, please click &lt;a class="link" href="https://kambri.top/search/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;; if you want to view friend links, please click &lt;a class="link" href="https://kambri.top/links/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. This is just a simple introduction to the menu on the left. Of course, you can also find my contact information, and you can switch languages (supporting Simplified Chinese, English, and Japanese) and toggle light/dark themes using the button at the bottom left. If you have any thoughts, feel free to leave a comment below (though utterances require a GitHub account).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>