<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on Kambri's Blog</title><link>https://kambri.top/en/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on Kambri's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>Kaige ZHENG</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kambri.top/en/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://kambri.top/en/about/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kambri.top/en/about/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⚠️ Please note that the content here was translated by a large language model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;h2 id="about-me"&gt;About Me
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am a senior undergraduate student majoring in Computer Science and Technology. My previous research focus was on high-performance computing, and now I am focusing on deep generative models, occasionally paying attention to AI Infra work. Recently, I have been learning and exploring the field of diffusion models, hoping to publish a good paper in the future. At the same time, I am also considering whether to pursue a Ph.D. or enter the workforce in the future. Although it&amp;rsquo;s not yet time to make a decision, I should think about it in advance to have better options. I also welcome fellow students who are similarly undecided to discuss this with me.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don&amp;rsquo;t have any sophisticated hobbies. In my spare time, I enjoy traveling, music, and games. Traveling to unfamiliar places can bring a lot of freshness, and I hope to visit every province in China before my student days end, and also travel around the world as much as possible. In terms of music, I mainly listen to Japanese music (but not JPOP), and I have been a fan of Yuki Kajiura (Fiction Junction) and Kokia for many years. &lt;a class="link" href="http://gallery.kambri.top/live/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;This album&lt;/a&gt; records the LIVE shows I&amp;rsquo;ve attended. Living is all about sustainably attending more LIVE shows. As for games, I used to play a lot, but recently I haven&amp;rsquo;t had much time due to my studies. I have tried many types of games in the past, and I want to list some of my favorites (I&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to do this for a long time), such as the Type-Moon series (FGO/Mahoutsukai no Yoru/Tsukihime), the Final Fantasy series (VII/XIV/XV), the Pokémon series (Sword and Shield/Scarlet and Violet/Arceus/ZA), etc. I&amp;rsquo;ve also played quite a few FPS and MOBA games, but I&amp;rsquo;m not very good at them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="about-the-site"&gt;About the Site
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;This site is built with &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/gohugoio/hugo" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;Hugo&lt;/a&gt; and uses the &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/CaiJimmy/hugo-theme-stack" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;Stack theme&lt;/a&gt; (&lt;code&gt;v3.33.0&lt;/code&gt;) with modifications. It is hosted on &lt;a class="link" href="https://pages.github.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;GitHub Pages&lt;/a&gt; and uses Alibaba Cloud CDN for domain distribution. The comment system is supported by &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/utterance" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;Utterances&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The site was officially established on &lt;code&gt;2024/11/23&lt;/code&gt; and underwent a &amp;ldquo;remake&amp;rdquo; at the beginning of 2026. The posts and comments from the old blog have been archived &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/KaigeZheng/Personal-Blog-Archive" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. I will write and upload (or update previous posts) whenever I have time, and I will also update the blog style based on some needs during my continuous exploration (but I won&amp;rsquo;t spend too much effort on it, as front-end development is not my main focus).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Archive</title><link>https://kambri.top/en/archives/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kambri.top/en/archives/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Link</title><link>https://kambri.top/en/links/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kambri.top/en/links/</guid><description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;⚠️ Please note that the content here was translated by a large language model.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;If you want to add a friend link, please &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/KaigeZheng/KaigeZheng.github.io/issues" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
&gt;create an issue here&lt;/a&gt; or contact &lt;code&gt;kambrikg DOT gmail DOT com&lt;/code&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>https://kambri.top/en/search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kambri.top/en/search/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>